Who's the best Ohio State player in this
year's NFL draft?
That's tough. I'm going to have to go
with the linebackers though. They're
both special.
I think I heard that five Ohio State
players are going in that first round,
so that might be a record.
Got a lot of talent by those Buckeye
guys, so hopefully they end up in a
great spot. Would you make calls to
these guys telling them like I've had a
great experience with building something
special here? Do you know any of those
guys like just through contacts and
such? Yeah, I think that Ohio State
especially does a great job of, you
know, keeping in contact and having the
guys and the coaches be present with,
you know, the former players. And you
know, I've I've been in touch with a few
of those guys and the main message
always and you tell them every year is
just enjoy the process.
It's going to be so exciting. It's a big
life changer. What an opportunity. I
mean, talk about setting up your family
and
you know,
family, everybody for life. It's You
want to work as hard as you can, but
just enjoy the process. Do you have a
relationship with any of those three
guys projected to go around near where
you all are picking and Not as close. I
mean, now I'm going on my sixth year in
the NFL, so I'm I was a little bit
closer to some of those guys year three,
you know, year two, year three coming in
the NFL, but
you're still tight with the Buckeye
guys. I mean, it's still an unreal
experience for them, so I'm just wishing
them all the best. Any draft plans for
you?
No, not for me. I'll just be hanging
out.
I got a baby what on the way here in
about four weeks, so I'll be attending
you know, back to Indy as much as I can
for for my wife. So, that'll that'll be
the big highlight for me. Pete, does it
sink in at all that that Demario's not
going to be next to you? You know, it
has been a little weird especially this
first week back.
Just being around him my first five
years in the NFL, it's he's always been
a big, you know, presence for me and
he's a guy that I credit a lot for, you
know, developing my game and and using
him a lot to
to you know, to elevate. And you know,
it it is a little bit tricky, a little
bit weird seeing it now, but you know,
we got a great room. We've always had a
great linebacker room.
I pride, you know, I
I'm sure he takes a lot of pride in it,
but he's the one that shaped it. So, now
we just got to keep the the expectations
up and
following that path. Obviously, the
familiarity with Kaden made that a
welcome addition, I assume. Yes, it was
so good to see Kaden.
He's had an awesome career and it's so
good to have him back here in in New
Orleans. We got a a great group, so I'm
just excited to work with them. Do you
have a pre-draft message like just
assuming maybe one of those Ohio State
Buckeye guys ends up in black and gold,
what would you maybe tell them about the
city, the team?
Yeah, well, first of all, New Orleans is
a great place to be drafted into. You
know, the history of this team, uh
you know, it's just a great
organization, uh great coaches, great
teammates.
We get guys from all different types of
teams. And one thing they say about New
Orleans is how great the city is to play
in.
So, that was what I'd be most excited
for. And you know, just being playing
with some former teammates. I've
done that a lot especially we got Chase
on the team, but back when, you know,
Warshaw and Malcolm Jenkins, we've had a
lot of Ohio State guys, so um
if that were the the case though, you
know, it would be a pretty great team.
Pretty cool to see all my Buckeyes. What
was the last, you know, with the offense
of the program starting again, just kind
of the optimism and it's you know,
coming in the second year and it's kind
of the vibe and the lights and
everything.
How's that feeling there? Yeah, I would
say the vibe's strong.
I think the key message is let's build
off the momentum that we had towards the
end of last year.
I think with the first week, you're just
seeing faces that you haven't seen in a
few months, so you're starting to, you
know, get grab that chemistry back and
and really work out and you know, go
through some tough times together. So, I
think it's just good to see
the familiar faces and you can go and,
you know, attack this thing.